

# ROHAN ADHIA

Highly analytical and process-oriented data analyst with in-depth knowledge of database types; research methodologies; and big data capture, curation, manipulation and visualization. Furnish insights, analytics and business intelligence used to advance opportunity identification, process reengineering and corporate growth.

# CONTACT

- Andheri East, Mumbai-400069
- rohan.adhia@gmail.com
- +91-951-951-0023
- in /rohanadhia
- https://rohanadhia.github.io/resume/

# PERSONAL PROFILE

Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. I am confident in my excellent technical abilities, as they are responsible for evaluating sets of information and implementing appropriate solutions. My applicable technical experience and skills can include the following: programming and coding; ability to translate unstructured information into structured information

## EDUCATION

Business Analytics & Data Science(2019) Edupristine

# **Ignite Program(2017)**

**Datamatics Business Solutions Limited** 

Bachelor of Science Information Technology (2014-15) Malini Kishor Sanghvi College of Commerce & Economics

**Higher Secondary School (2010 – 2011)** Vidyanidhi Jr. College

### Secondary School Certificate (2007-2008)

St. Dominic Savio High School

# SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

Excellent technical abilities, strong interpersonal skills, and effective project management abilities.

#### **Intermediate MS Excel Mentor**

Trained employees at Angel Broking Ltd on advanced features of MS Excel.

#### **LANGUAGES & TECHNOLOGY**

- Data Analytics using R language.
- Python
- Java,
- ASP.NET with C#
- C & C++
- . Google App Script -(Based on Javascript
- used to automate day to day tasks.)
- . HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- Front End Framework(Bootstrap)

# ADDITIONA L SKILLS

- GRAPHIC DESIGNING -Logo Designs
  Social Media Post Design Website Designing,
  Visiting Card Design Poster Design, etc.
- Music Production using FL Studio

## HOBBIES

- Designing
- Music Production
- Reading
- Web development
- · Watching web-series

- Node JS JS Runtime Environment
- Express JS JS Framework for NodJS
- JQuery
- APIs & Interfaces

#### **SOFTWARES**

- MS Excel & Google Sheets
- R Software
- MS office
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Visual Studio
- Canva
- Github

# WORK EXPERIENCE

# Marsh McLennan Companies - Assistant Manager - Placement Data & Analytics

JULY 2021 - PRESENT

- Working extensively on UK's subscription insurance market placement data capture and analysis.
- Developed a strong understanding of the insurance broking business.
- Use of advanced Excel skills, VBA, & various programming languages to analyse & capture placement data.
- Involved in different projects related to process optimisation and market trends analysis.

# **Motilal Oswal Financial Services Ltd - Data Analyst**

DEC 2020 - MAY 2021

- Looking after 3 processes Activation, Reactivation & Equity Broking.
- Using logical skills to create live dashboard to track & analyse the crucial data points.
- Collaboration & maintaining data.
- Making KRA & KPI based business analysis.
- Tracking performance and making incentive score cards for all the 3 desks.
- Conduct data analysis to improve performance and achieve excellence.

# **Angel Broking Ltd - Specialist - Analytics**

SEPT 2018 - DEC 2020

- Collaborating data from various branches & regions to ensure streamlined implementations of services, profiling source information and setting characteristics, and executing big data processes like parsing, filtering, text connotation, and enrichment.
- Responsible to look after business and financial data for the branch.
- Developed a live sales dashboard used for real time tracking and analysis of sales
- Mapping of client based on their region
- Analysis of various types sales and brokerage data for PAN india
- Designing and making analytical presentation for board meetings
- Automation of data to generate reports .

# **WNS Global Services - Senior Associate - Operations**

SEPT 2017 - AUG 2018

- Responded to customer service enquiries/ complaints/suggestions/feedback via email within the assigned TAT.
- Identified and highlighted any concern affecting the brand.
- Provided accurate, valid and complete information by using the right methods and tools.

# Datamatics Business Solutions Limited - Associate Web Research

JAN 2016 - MARCH 2017

- Worked on various projects into Data Research, Data Mining, & Data Cleansing
- Client interaction on regular basis
- Worked majorly with pilot projects & FTE projects
- Sampled data for new clients & provided efficient solutions working with the solutions desk
- Nominated & certified the Ignite program